<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<updates>
  <update version="3.1">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Redesigned Map Transition Auto-Splitting evaluation to being one-way</change>
      <change>Made Undo Split also affecting Auto-Splitting evaluation</change>
      <change>Added Higher-Precision Time and Tick Count</change>
      <change>Fixed a bug where leaving the Auto-Start map field empty resets the run upon game exit.</change>
      <change>Fixed a bug where changing tickrates affects the existing time on the timer.</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.1.1">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Added an option to start on portal open in Portal</change>
      <change>Renovated Custom Commands</change>
      <change>Modified Auto-End for Hell's Mines</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.1.2">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Overhauled Custom Commands</change>
      <change>Function to split on elevator starts and split on Death% ending in Portal (limited)</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.1.3">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Minor fixes and changes to settings UI</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.2.0">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Overhaul to timing methods to increase timing accuracies and fix issues related to pause spamming</change>
      <change>Fixed double splitting in HL2 Survivor</change>
      <change>Added an option to disable pausing timer when starting from game pause</change>
      <change>Code cleanups and refactoring</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.2.0.1">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Added some checks to prevent extra ticks being accounted into time</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.2.1">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Added support for Southernmost Combine.</change>
      <change>Fixed a problem with storing current / old player states upon map load leading to potential premature Auto-starts.</change>
      <change>Allowed variable precision on the Higher Precision Timer.</change>
      <change>Fixed Game Process List Default button not working.</change>
      <change>Added a description field for the various Timing Method options.</change>
      <change>Modified the Custom Command handler to use binary exports for console printing functions.</change>
      <change>Changed Death% split in Portal to only happen on the first map.</change>
      <change>Fixed the default value for TSP's No Space Ending Custom Command.</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.2.2">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Added support for Very Hard Mod</change>
      <change>Added an option to split upon intitial map loads</change>
      <change>Fixed a bug where the splitter stops working if Livesplit crashes or closed unexpectedly when the game is running</change>
      <change>Fixed a bug where typing into the Start Map textbox may cause an Exception to be tripped</change>
      <change>Fixed a bug related to start time offset being added twice</change>
      <change>Changed Black Mesa's xensplit in accordance with game rules</change>
      <change>Modified Auto-End for Upmine Struggle</change>
      <change>Unhandled or unexpected Exceptions will now be reported through a Warning popup</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.2.2.1">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Added an option to have Real Time be affected by built-in Auto-start time offset</change>
      <change>Added an option to disable splitting on special events.</change>
      <change>Fixed some UI element sizing.</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.2.2.2">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Fixed Save Deleting splitting when Splitting on Generic Map Split is enabled.</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.2.3">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Added an option to count server initialization ticks</change>
      <change>Added an option to add extra ticks per game load</change>
      <change>Added an option to Auto-Split instead of Auto-Resetting the timer</change>
      <change>Redesigned timer monitoring to no longer rely on memory injection</change>
      <change>Fixed some issues with time keeping, particularly with decimal precision</change>
      <change>Split Auto Start / Stop / Reset into 3 separate settings</change>
      <change>Cleaned up Setting-handling code</change>
      <change>Minor adjustments to settings UI</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.2.3.1">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Made Auto-Reset reset split-related states, even if it is disabled.</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.2.3.2">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Fixed Splitter sometimes missing splits.</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.2.3.3">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Fixed Dangerous World's Auto-Start firing on loading a save anywhere on the first map.</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.3.0">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Added Demo Recording interoperability for timing, so run time can more closely match demo time.</change>
      <change>Added a feature to print the information of the latest Demo to the Console.</change>
      <change>Added a feature to display the current Demo's name and tick count on the layout.</change>
      <change>Added an option to open SourceSplit's settings under the Control drowdown in LiveSplit.</change>
      <change>Added an option to add RTA to IGT when the game is not running.</change>
      <change>Added an extra condition for Auto-Starting when transitioning to a map or loading a save with a particular name.</change>
      <change>Added an option to disable Auto-Resetting when starting a New Game on the first map.</change>
      <change>Added support for Local Motive, Portal: Crumbs of Truth.</change>
      <change>Added extra split points for The Beginner's Guide.</change>
      <change>Redesigned map whitelist/blacklisting to allow/disallow specific transitions.</change>
      <change>Redesigned Map Times window.</change>      
      <change>Redesigned settings and added an About page.</change>      
      <change>Changed the timing for all Portal games/mods to abide by new rules.</change>
      <change>Changed the method for detecting Auto-Start in Portal to use file hash.</change>
      <change>Made Auto-Splitting history roll back when undoing splits.</change>
      <change>Some custom commands' values are now saved like settings.</change>
      <change>Made time and values shown by Additional Timers monospaced.</change>
      <change>Made the Tick Count display also show the tick count for the current Session.</change>
      <change>Removed Game Process List for automated game process acquisition logic.</change>
      <change>Split Timing Method into separate options.</change>
      <change>Fixed various bugs related to split tracking.</change>
      <change>Massive internal code revisions and refactoring.</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.3.1">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Added custom split points for Lost Coast.</change>
      <change>Added support for Portal RTX, Entropy Zero 2, Dark Evening, Episode 3: The Closure, AJB Trajectory trilogy, Forest Train</change>
      <change>Removed support for Portal 2, Portal Stories: Mel, and Aperature Tag as they were out of date and obsoleted by newer tools.</change>
      <change>Fixed some issues related to Custom Commands.</change>
      <change>Internal code revisions and cleanup.</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.3.2">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Added support for Evacuation, Minerva: METASTASIS</change>
      <change>Added Auto-Start support for 75FOV Portal 3420 vault save</change>
      <change>Corrected vault save timing for Portal games/mods</change>
      <change>Internal code revisions and cleanup.</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
  <update version="3.3.3">
    <files>
      <file path="Components/LiveSplit.SourceSplit.dll" status="changed" />
    </files>
    <changelog>
      <change>Added support for Amalgam, Avenue Odessa, City 17 Is Far Away, Dark 17, Jolly's Hardcore Mod, Sebastian, Nightmare House 1 &amp; 2, NEOTOKYO° Kshatriya, Uzvara, Abberation, Awakening, Call-In, Combine Destiny, Daylight, Expectation, Depot, Riot Act, Siren, Mountain Caves, Missile strike imminent, Overawe, Penetration, Person of Interest, Ravenholm: The Lost Chapter, Research and Development, The Road to Abyss, Spherical Nightmares, Station 51, The Lighthouse, Tr1p, Whoopservatory, Bear Party Adventure.</change>
      <change>Added support for (hopefully) all RTSL and Map Labs mapping competition compilations.</change>
      <change>Added text to show the currently detected game/mod under the Abouts page</change>
      <change>Fixed Evacuation's Auto-End not always working</change>
      <change>Corrected Auto-Start time offset for Portal's portal open auto-start.</change>
      <change>Internal code minimizing, revisions, and cleanup.</change>
    </changelog>
  </update>
</updates>
